<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Products on DeepLearn Research &amp; Development</title>
    <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/product/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Products on DeepLearn Research &amp; Development</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>DeepLearn LTD</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:10:06 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://deeplearn.ltd/product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AIwrite is here!</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/product/aiwrite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:10:06 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/product/aiwrite/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many people use AI to help them write documents particularly professional documents, but using standard online tools for writing is too cumbersome involving many copy/paste operations and tend to generate texts that are to generic and cannot be used directly before extensive manual editing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order to help is this type of task, we have developed AIWrite, a very simple text generator using your choice of AI agent, that not only lets you properly and easily specify the structure of technical documents, but also makes it very easy to provide the AI information of your specific area of expertise, in the form of a collection of reference documents, so that the AI gent will write like a pro, not like a newbie!.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regdbot alpha demo website</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/product/regdbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 10:28:05 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/product/regdbot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our database AI specialist &lt;a href=&#34;https://deeplearn.ltd/team/reg/&#34;&gt;Reggie D. Bot&lt;/a&gt; is now available for a demo at &lt;a href=&#34;https://regdbot.deeplearn.ltd&#34;&gt;regdbot.deeplearn.ltd&lt;/a&gt;. This is an alpha release, so at this point you can&amp;rsquo;t upload new datasets or register as an user. This release is for testing purposes only.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feel free to have a chat with Reggie about the available demo datasets. In the upcoming  Beta version, you will be able to upload new datasets, and also connect to external data sources.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
