<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DeepLearn Research &amp; Development</title>
    <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DeepLearn Research &amp; Development</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>DeepLearn LTD</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 09:12:16 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://deeplearn.ltd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugging_face</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/hugging_face/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 09:12:16 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/hugging_face/</guid>
      <description>We have just created an organization page on Hugging Face. You can find us at DeeplearnRnD. We are planning to release some of our models there, so stay tuned for updates!&#xA;Feel free to follow us there as well!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New RegDBot Release: v0.6.0</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/regdbot_v0.6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:57:06 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/regdbot_v0.6.0/</guid>
      <description>We have just release a new version of Reggie D. Bot, v0.6.0. This release includes the following features:&#xA;Improved user interface, with a new design and better user experience. Log of code snippets: Now every code snippet generated by Reggie D. Bot is saved in a log, so that you can easily access it later. The log entry is stored alongside the question that motivated it and an explanation. Many bugfixes and performance improvements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regdbot alpha demo website</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/product/regdbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 10:28:05 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/product/regdbot/</guid>
      <description>Our database AI specialist Reggie D. Bot is now available for a demo at regdbot.deeplearn.ltd. This is an alpha release, so at this point you can&amp;rsquo;t upload new datasets or register as an user. This release is for testing purposes only.&#xA;Feel free to have a chat with Reggie about the available demo datasets. In the upcoming Beta version, you will be able to upload new datasets, and also connect to external data sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demo of Reggie D. Bot is online</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/reggie_demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:59:57 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/reggie_demo/</guid>
      <description>After a few months of hard work, we are pleased to announce that we have made the first release of Reggie D. Bot. The demo is available at regdbot.deeplearn.ltd. It is still an alpha release, So at this point you can&amp;rsquo;t upload new datasets or register as an user. This release is for testing purposes only, and is linked with our project in the Backdrop build v5 program.&#xA;Next steps before having a beta release, are to add the ability to upload new datasets, and to register as an user.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuing in Backdropbuild v5</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/backdropbuildv5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:44:12 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/backdropbuildv5/</guid>
      <description>In our previous post we mentioned that we were joining the Backdrop Build program this year where we are proposing to turn our REG AI into a product. Even with our best efforts we felt that the Reggie D. Bot was not ready to be a product yet. So we rejoined Backdrop Build v5 to continue our work on Reggie D. Bot, while benefitting of building withing the backdrop community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Started!</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/build_started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:50:07 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/build_started/</guid>
      <description>Our journey has just begun in Backdrop Build v4! Israel and I are super excited and we are looking forward to having a first release very soon. Today I have managed to prepared the demos database that we are going to use for the first release. It has 20 years worth of dengue incidence data for Reggie to chew on!&#xA;Another exciting milestone is that we&amp;rsquo;ll have the first usable interface for our product out for testing by the end of the week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:12:13 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Draft</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/myfirstdraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:00:57 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/myfirstdraft/</guid>
      <description>Deeplearn has recently started a joint-venture with Publicase, a company that specializes in helping sciecntists write better scientific articles. The goal of this joint-venture is to develop an AI model that can act as an interactive writing assitant for scientists.&#xA;The AI model will be able to help scientists write better scientific articles by providing suggestions on how to improve their writing. The AI model will be trained on a large dataset of scientific articles, selected by the the author, and will be able to provide suggestions on grammar, style, and content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joining the Backdrop Build program</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/backdropbuild/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 11:38:09 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/backdropbuild/</guid>
      <description>Deeplearn is joing the Backdrop Build program this year where we a proposing to turn our REG AI into a product. Joining efforts with us in this challenge is Israel Teixeira from NAN systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joining the Backdrop Build program</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/backdropbuild/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 11:38:09 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/backdropbuild/</guid>
      <description>Deeplearn is joing the Backdrop Build program this year where we a proposing to turn our REG AI into a product. Joining efforts with us in this challenge is Israel Teixeira from NAN systems.&#xA;Our challenge is to make our AI agent Reggie D. Bot into a product that can be used by the general public. We are excited to be part of this program and we are looking forward to the results of this challenge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Embedding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/team/libby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 11:12:08 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/team/libby/</guid>
      <description>Working together with the Retrieval Enhanced Generation Team, the construction of knowledge embeddings typically from textual corpora, specializes in construction of embeddings, and sophisticated querying and text generation, review, and optimization based on client-specific knowledge databases.&#xA;Team Lead Libby D. Bot I as AI specialized in assisting users to build textual corpora and integrating into generative workflows through embedding.&#xA;Liby also coordinates multiple AI agents and different LLM models, to collectiveley improve textual generation through a methodology known as reflection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval Enhanced Generation</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/team/reg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:59:31 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/team/reg/</guid>
      <description>Retrieval Enhanced Generation Abstract A popular application in AI is the generation of text, and data analysis products based on existing knowledge. This is a challenging task, as it requires the model to understand the context of the input data and generate meaningful output. Structured Data such as relational databases and unstructured data such as text, images, and videos are used as context for the generative models.&#xA;At DeepLearn we call this task Retrieval Enhanced Generation (REG).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/reg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:55:13 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/reg/</guid>
      <description>Deeplearn: An AI team for Intelligent services. Deeplearn is an AI first company. This means that our mission is to develop the most efficient and friendly AI assistants for our customers. We are a team of AI experts that are passionate about AI and its potential to change the world. We believe that AI can be used to solve some of the most challenging problems that we face today. Our goal is to make AI accessible to everyone, and to help our customers achieve their goals with the help of AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year&#39;s Challenges</title>
      <link>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/new-years-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:24:56 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deeplearn.ltd/blog/posts/new-years-challenges/</guid>
      <description>2023 is upon us! In this new Year, DeepLearn starts as a new external face to a team os experienced researchers with many years of experience of bringing AI to verticals typically ignored by big AI corporations.&#xA;Along with the usual challenges related to simple survival, we are driven to find and develop new AI solutions than can solve problems instead of creating them (like the Fake news industry). In this road we hope to continue to meet inspiring people that can help us identify the worthy problems and the talented ones that will partner with us to build the solutions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
